db.questions.insertMany([
	{
		question_num: 20,
		question: "BB-8 is an astromech droid from what film?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Star Wars",
		choices: ["Star Wars","Lord of the Rings", "Harry Potter", "Interstellar"]
	},

	{
		question_num: 21,
		question: "Who does the voice over for Dory from 'Finding Nemo' and 'Finding Dory'?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Ellen DeGeneres",
		choices: ["Beyonce", "Oprah", "Jennifer Lawrence", "Ellen DeGeneres"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 22,
		question: "The title role of the 1900's movie, 'Pretty Woman', was played by which actress?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Julia Roberts",
		choices: ["Whitney Houston", "Julie Andrews", "Sandra Bullock", "Meryl Streep"]

	},
	{
		question_num: 23,
		question: "What school does Harry Potter attend?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Hogwarts",
		choices: ["Ministry of Magic", "Hogwarts", "Middle Earth", "Azkaban"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 24,
		question: "What school does Harry Potter attend?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Hogwarts",
		choices: ["Ministry of Magic", "Hogwarts", "Middle Earth", "Azkaban"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 25,
		question: "Which horror movie character is a serial killer possessing a doll?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Easy",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Chucky",
		choices: ["Chucky", "Annabelle", "Leatherface", "Ghostface"]
	},





	{
		question_num: 26,
		question: "In the Lion King, what was Simba's fathers name?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Mufasa"
	},

	{
		question_num: 27,
		question: "In what year was the first Harry Potter movie released?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "2001",
		choices: ["2000", "2001", "2002", "2003"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 28,
		question: "Bruce Banner turns into what fictional superhero when he becomes angry?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "The Hulk"
	},
	{
		question_num: 29,
		question: "Which actor played Marty McFly in the 1980s sci-fi classic 'Back to the Future'?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Hogwarts",
		choices: ["Matt Damon", "George Clooney", "Michael J. Fox", "Daniel Day Lewis"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 30,
		question: "In the movie 'Mean Girls', what day do they wear pink?",
		type: "Multiple choice",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Wednesday",
		choices: ["Monday", "Thursdays", "Friday", "Wednesday"]
	},
	{
		question_num: 31,
		question: "Who voice the character 'Joy' in the 2015 film 'Inside Out'?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Medium",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Amy Poehler"
	},
	{
		question_num: 32,
		question: "Which English actor played Itzhak Stern in the 1993 film Schindler's List?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Ben Kingsley"
	},

	{
		question_num: 33,
		question: "Complete the title of the fifth film in the Pirates of the Caribbean series: 'Dead Men Tell No...'?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Tales"
	},
	{
		question_num: 34,
		question: "What is the name of the 2015 film about a frontiersman on a fur trading expedition in the 1820s and his fight for survival after being mauled by a bear?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "The Revenant"
	},
	{
		question_num: 35,
		question: "Canadian actress who starred in The Notebook, and The Vow, and more recently as Ani Bezzerides in the TV series True Detective?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Rachel McAdams"
	},
	{
		question_num: 36,
		question: "Released in 1999 and stars Keanu Reeves as a computer hacker.",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "The Matrix"
	},
	{
		question_num: 37,
		question: "Who is being portrayed by actor Benedict Cumberbatch in the movie 'The Imitation Game'?",
		type: "Text Answer",
		difficulty: "Hard",
		category: "Movies",
		answer: "Alan Turing"
	}

])
	
